CHRISTIAN DOMINGUEZ

CONTACT

(786) 548 - 8327



ChristianDominguez1003@gmail.com



Homestead, FL 33033

EDUCATION

TERRA ENVIRONMENTAL **RESEARCH INSTITUTE**

2018 - 2022

FLORIDA INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY

Cybersecurity

2022 -Current

SKILLS

Communication Skills

Flexibility/Adaptability

Highly Responsible and Reliable

Problem-Solving

Works well under pressure

Extensive Hospitality Background

High-Volume Dining

(Florida) SafeStaff Certified

Bilingual English/Spanish

SUMMARY

I am currently exploring the possibility of obtaining a position in a company where I can utilize my experience and skills toward becoming a valuable team member. As a team player, I am able to integrate and adapt effective people, situations and work environment. My work is quick and efficient and I provide service in a professional and efficient manner. I have included my resume for your review and welcome the chance to meet you to discuss how I can contribute to your company. Thank you for taking the time to consider my application. I hope to hear from you at your convenience.

EXPERIENCE

PUBLIX

2021 - 2022

Cashier

- Provide a warm and sincere greeting.
- Operate cash register or POS system to receive payment by cash, check and credit card.
- Work closely with front-end staff to assist guest in finding specific products, answer questions and offer product advice.
- Verify guest age requirement for alcohol or tobacco purchases.
- Track company inventories, moved excess stock and arranged products to improve sales.

WHIP N' DIP

2022 - Current

Server / Cashier

- Deliver exceptional, friendly and fast service.
- Maintain knowledge of current menu items, garnishes, ingredients and preparation methods.
- Appropriately suggested additional items to guests to increase
- Communicate with staff regarding guest allergies and dietary preferences.
- Regularly check on guests to ensure satisfaction with the food quality.